Support Admin Watch on kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
دعم المشرف شاهد على kissasia.cam أو kisskh.org
[Echoes of the Self]
[أصداء الذات]
I am your future self,
أنا نفسك المستقبلية
three years from now.
بعد ثلاث سنوات من الآن.
What nonsense are you talking about?
ما هذا الهراء الذي تتحدث عنه؟
I know you don't believe me.
أعرف أنك لا تصدقني.
That cold winter when you were 7,
في ذلك الشتاء البارد عندما كنت في السابعة من عمرك،
the west wing room was freezing.
كانت الغرفة في الجناح الغربي متجمدة.
Mother's old illness relapsed from the cold.
انتكس مرض والدتي القديم بسبب البرد.
You stole coal from Madam Cui's room
لقد سرقت الفحم من غرفة السيدة كوي
and were punished to wash clothes in the servants' quarters.
وكانوا يعاقبون بغسل الملابس في غرف الخدم.
The water was bone-chillingly cold,
كان الماء باردًا جدًا لدرجة تجمد العظام،
but you didn't shed a single tear.
ولكنك لم تذرف دمعة واحدة.
When you were 13, during a banquet at the mansion,
عندما كنت في الثالثة عشر من عمرك، أثناء مأدبة في القصر،
you were suddenly inspired
لقد ألهمتك فجأة
and recited some poetry.
وألقى بعض الشعر.
Madam Cui accused you of stealing Ruoyao's spotlight
اتهمتك السيدة كوي بسرقة الأضواء من روياو
and punished you to copy books for 3 days.
وعاقبتك بنسخ الكتب لمدة 3 أيام.
You didn't eat a single grain of rice
لم تأكل حبة أرز واحدة
and never uttered a word of complaint.
ولم ينطق بكلمة شكوى قط.
How do you know all this?
كيف تعرف كل هذا؟
I am you.
انا انت.
I've walked your path.
لقد مشيت في طريقك.
I know why you staked your life to fight,
أنا أعلم لماذا خاطرت بحياتك من أجل القتال،
but I also know your ending.
ولكنني أعرف نهايتك أيضًا.
That's why I don't want you
لهذا السبب لا أريدك
or us to repeat the same mistakes.
أو أن نكرر نفس الأخطاء.
I don't know where you heard all this.
لا أعلم أين سمعت كل هذا.
But I
ولكن انا
don't believe you.
لا أصدقك.
When Zhou's Mansion was confiscated in the previous life,
عندما تمت مصادرة قصر تشو في الحياة السابقة،
the garden rockery was made of gold and jade.
كانت حديقة الصخور مصنوعة من الذهب واليشم.
Coming back in this life,
العودة إلى هذه الحياة،
I didn't see it.
لم أرى ذلك.
But yesterday,
ولكن بالأمس،
I saw it in the garden at Zhou's Mansion.
رأيته في حديقة قصر تشو.
Gold and jade rockery.
صخرة من الذهب واليشم.
How is it still here?
كيف لا يزال هنا؟
Mother's death is connected to the loan sharking case.
ترتبط وفاة الأم بقضية القروض الربوية.
Zhou Kui is the real mastermind behind it all.
تشو كوي هو العقل المدبر الحقيقي وراء كل هذا.
But she was clearly dead at that time.
لكن من الواضح أنها ماتت في ذلك الوقت.
Father.
أب.
You were looking for me?
هل كنت تبحث عني؟
Xi,
شي،
you've been away from home for so many days.
لقد كنت بعيدًا عن المنزل لعدة أيام.
You must have suffered a lot.
لا بد أنك عانيت كثيرًا.
I asked the kitchen
سألت المطبخ
to make some chicken soup for you,
لأصنع لك حساء الدجاج،
and your favorite
والمفضل لديك
peanut pudding
بودنغ الفول السوداني
and
و
osmanthus cake.
كعكة العثمانية.
Thank you for your concern, Father.
شكرا لاهتمامك يا أبي.
But I'm allergic to peanuts.
ولكن لدي حساسية من الفول السوداني.
And I don't eat osmanthus cake either.
وأنا لا آكل كعكة العثمانية أيضًا.
You must have forgotten.
لا بد أنك نسيت.
My bad.
خطئي.
I must be getting confused.
لابد أنني أشعر بالارتباك.
You're just concerned about me.
أنت فقط قلق علي.
You must have been
لا بد أنك كنت
exhausted from preparing for the Princess's wedding.
مرهق من التحضير لحفل زفاف الأميرة.
About what you mentioned earlier,
أما بالنسبة لما ذكرته سابقا،
regarding making me the principal daughter of the Zhou family,
فيما يتعلق بجعلني الابنة الرئيسية لعائلة تشو،
there's no need to rush.
ليست هناك حاجة للتسرع.
We can discuss it after you're less busy.
يمكننا مناقشة هذا الأمر بعد أن تصبح أقل انشغالاً.
Xi,
شي،
Why do I feel that since you've returned,
لماذا أشعر أنه منذ عودتك،
you seem different from before?
هل يبدو أنك مختلف عن ذي قبل؟
Father, you must be joking.
أبي، لا بد أنك تمزح.
How am I different?
كيف أنا مختلف؟
When I offered to make you the Zhou family's principal daughter,
عندما عرضت عليك أن أجعلك الابنة الرئيسية لعائلة تشو،
you were in a hurry,
كنت في عجلة من أمرك
not as composed as you are today.
ليس بنفس الهدوء الذي أنت عليه اليوم.
With your behavior,
مع سلوكك،
I actually think
انا اعتقد فعلا
you're more like
أنت أكثر مثل
the Princess of Daqing.
أميرة داتشينغ.
I was immature before.
لقد كنت غير ناضجة من قبل.
Now
الآن
it's time to grow up.
حان الوقت لكي تكبر.
I should think of Father
ينبغي لي أن أفكر في الأب
and the Zhou family.
وعائلة تشو.
After all, Mother is gone now.
بعد كل شيء، أمي رحلت الآن.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدا،
you're
انت
my only support.
دعمي الوحيد.
You're such a good girl.
أنت فتاة جيدة جدًا.
You just came back.
لقد عدت للتو.
Get some rest.
احصل على بعض الراحة.
I
أنا
have important matters to attend to.
لدي أمور مهمة يجب الاهتمام بها.
I'll take my leave.
سوف آخذ إجازتي.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
It seems
يبدو أنه
Zhou Kui is already suspicious of my identity.
تشو كوي يشك في هويتي بالفعل .
I need to act quickly
أحتاج إلى التصرف بسرعة
before things get complicated.
قبل أن تصبح الأمور معقدة.
This mansion isn't as impenetrable as it seems.
هذا القصر ليس منيعًا كما يبدو.
I need to find a chance to escape soon.
أحتاج إلى إيجاد فرصة للهروب قريبًا.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
it's time for your medicine.
لقد حان وقت دوائك.
His Highness instructed me to take good care of you.
لقد أمرني سموه بالعناية بك جيدًا.
If you're feeling bored,
إذا كنت تشعر بالملل،
you can walk around inside the mansion.
يمكنك التجول داخل القصر.
I can accompany you.
أستطيع مرافقتك.
But as for leaving the mansion,
وأما بالنسبة لمغادرة القصر،
don't even think about it.
لا تفكر حتى في هذا الأمر.
This is kidnapping and imprisonment!
هذا هو الاختطاف والسجن!
I won't take the medicine.
لن آخذ الدواء
Just let me die.
فقط دعني أموت.
Your Highness can skip
سموكم قادر على التخطي
the medicine as you like.
الدواء كما تريد.
Anyway,
على أي حال،
your life has been saved.
لقد تم انقاذ حياتك.
As for the remaining poison in your body,
وأما السم المتبقي في جسدك،
the damage
الضرر
isn't that serious.
أليس هذا خطيرا؟
At worst,
في أسوأ الأحوال،
you'll just be covered in sores
سوف تكون مغطى بالقروح فقط
and your face will be completely ruined.
وسوف يتم تدمير وجهك بالكامل.
Don't worry, Your Highness.
لا تقلق يا صاحب السمو.
When it's safe,
عندما يكون الأمر آمنًا،
you'll naturally be allowed to leave.
سيتم السماح لك بالمغادرة بشكل طبيعي.
Really?
حقًا؟
Yes.
نعم.
[Zhou's Mansion]
[قصر تشو]
The loan sharking case,
قضية القروض الربوية
the Mid-Autumn assassination attempt,
محاولة اغتيال منتصف الخريف،
and that jade pendant—
وتلك القلادة اليشمية
everything is connected to Zhou Kui.
كل شيء مرتبط بتشو كوي.
I must find clues
يجب أن أجد أدلة
to discover what Zhou Kui is plotting.
لاكتشاف ما يخطط له تشو كوي.
[Find the missing spy. Get the badge back. Emergency. No delay.]
[ابحث عن الجاسوس المفقود. استرجع شارتك. حالة طوارئ. لا تأخير.]
Eastern Palace?
القصر الشرقي؟
It's the Crown Prince again.
إنه ولي العهد مرة أخرى.
Someone was here.
كان هناك شخص هنا.
My Lord!
سيدي!
What is it?
ما هذا؟
The Crown Princess went to the back garden.
ذهبت ولي العهد إلى الحديقة الخلفية.
Hurry.
عجل.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو،
they're gone.
لقد رحلوا.
Why are you here?
لماذا انت هنا؟
I was worried you might be in danger.
لقد كنت قلقا من أنك قد تكون في خطر.
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
I have the charm you gave me.
لقد حصلت على السحر الذي أعطيته لي.
When Zhou's Mansion was confiscated in the previous life,
عندما تمت مصادرة قصر تشو في الحياة السابقة،
the garden rockery was made of gold and jade.
كانت حديقة الصخور مصنوعة من الذهب واليشم.
It's actually true.
إنه صحيح فعلا.
When Madam Cui was alive,
عندما كانت السيدة كوي على قيد الحياة،
there was no gold and jade rockery in the mansion.
لم يكن هناك أي صخور ذهبية أو يشمية في القصر.
In the loan sharking case,
في قضية القروض الربوية،
the one who took bribes was actually Father.
الذي أخذ الرشوة هو في الواقع الأب.
How does Fu Wei know all this?
كيف يعرف فو وي كل هذا؟
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
she really came from three years in the future?
هل جاءت حقا من ثلاث سنوات في المستقبل؟
Lord Zhou,
اللورد تشو،
why did you request to see me
لماذا طلبت رؤيتي؟
so late at night?
في وقت متأخر من الليل؟
Greetings, Your Highness.
تحياتي، صاحب السمو.
A servant just reported
لقد أبلغني أحد الخدم للتو
that you went to the back garden.
أنك ذهبت إلى الحديقة الخلفية.
I wonder,
انا اتعجب،
did you lose something important?
هل فقدت شيئا مهما؟
Since when are my affairs
منذ متى كانت شؤوني
any of your business, Lord Zhou?
أي من أعمالك، اللورد تشو؟
Your Highness, I certainly
صاحب السمو، أنا بالتأكيد
wouldn't dare to interfere.
لن أجرؤ على التدخل.
But what if
ولكن ماذا لو
it's my daughter's affairs?
هل هذا شأن ابنتي؟
Xi.
شي.
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ!
I've lived long enough
لقد عشت طويلا بما فيه الكفاية
not to be so foolish that I can't
لا أكون أحمقًا لدرجة أنني لا أستطيع
recognize my own daughter.
التعرف على ابنتي.
I just don't understand
انا فقط لا افهم
why you switched identities
لماذا قمت بتبديل الهويات
with Princess Fu Wei.
مع الأميرة فو وي.
But one thing is certain.
ولكن هناك شيء واحد مؤكد.
If
لو
you want to secure
تريد تأمين
your position as the Crown Princess,
منصبك كأميرة التاج،
you need to cooperate with me.
يجب عليك التعاون معي.
You don't need to be nervous.
لا داعي لأن تكون متوترًا.
I called you here today
لقد اتصلت بك هنا اليوم
not to expose you,
لا لتعريضك،
but to
ولكن الى
lend you a helping hand.
أقدم لك يد المساعدة.
After all,
بعد كل شيء،
we are the real father and daughter,
نحن الأب وابنته الحقيقيين
sharing honor and disgrace together.
مشاركة الشرف والعار معًا.
Don't you agree, Xi?
ألا توافقني الرأي يا شي؟
Father,
أب،
you're right.
أنت على حق.
Xi, you're so sensible.
شي، أنت عاقل جدًا.
That puts my mind at ease.
وهذا يطمئنني.
Go to the Eastern Palace with peace of mind
اذهب إلى القصر الشرقي براحة البال
and fulfill your duties as the Crown Princess.
وأداء واجباتك كأميرة التاج.
As for everything else,
أما بالنسبة لكل شيء آخر،
I
أنا
will naturally take care of it for you.
سوف يعتني بها بشكل طبيعي بالنسبة لك.
What do you plan to do?
ماذا تخطط أن تفعل؟
The Crown Prince has already suspected me.
لقد شك بي ولي العهد بالفعل.
How should
كيف ينبغي
I deal with him?
أتعامل معه؟
Recently, something else happened at the Crown Prince's Mansion.
ومؤخرًا، حدث أمر آخر في قصر ولي العهد.
I wonder if you know about it, Father.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت تعرف ذلك، يا أبي.
The youngest son of the Marquis of Zhenguo, Cui Yuan'an,
الابن الأصغر للماركيز تشنغو، كوي يوان آن،
broke into the Crown Prince's Mansion,
اقتحموا قصر ولي العهد،
intending to assassinate the Crown Prince.
كان ينوي اغتيال ولي العهد.
He was carrying a token from the Eastern Palace
وكان يحمل رمزًا من القصر الشرقي
accusing the Crown Prince of masterminding the loan sharking case.
واتهم ولي العهد بالتخطيط لقضية القروض الربوية.
He also claimed
كما ادعى
that the Crown Prince made
أن ولي العهد قام
the Marquis of Zhenguo's family take the blame,
تتحمل عائلة ماركيز تشنغو اللوم،
resulting in their execution.
مما أدى إلى إعدامهم.
How would I know about this matter?
كيف يمكنني أن أعرف عن هذا الموضوع؟
Besides,
بجانب،
it has nothing
ليس لديه شيء
to do with me at all.
هل لي أن أفعل ذلك على الإطلاق؟
You're right, Father.
أنت على حق يا أبي.
Well,
حسنًا،
I'll take my leave now.
سوف آخذ إجازتي الآن.
Wait.
انتظر.
As for Fu Wei's matter,
أما بالنسبة لمسألة فو وي،
don't concern yourself with it.
لا تهتم بهذا الأمر.
I
أنا
have my own plans.
لدي خططي الخاصة.
Yes.
نعم.
[Order]
[طلب]
It seems Father and the Crown Prince
يبدو أن الأب وولي العهد
both have secrets they cannot reveal.
كلاهما لديه أسرار لا يستطيعان الكشف عنها.
Father, you want to arrange my marriage?
أبي هل تريد أن ترتب زواجي؟
Yes.
نعم.
I
أنا
sympathize with your loneliness.
التعاطف مع وحدتك.
Therefore,
لذلك،
[Deep Roots; Lush Branches]
[جذور عميقة؛ فروع خصبة]
I've arranged
لقد رتبت
this marriage for you.
هذا الزواج لك.
You'll marry the Governor of Yingzhou
سوف تتزوج حاكم ينغتشو
as his second wife.
كزوجته الثانية.
The Governor of Yingzhou's
حاكم ينغتشو
second wife?
زوجة ثانية؟
Mm.
مم.
Father,
أب،
the Governor of Yingzhou is too old.
حاكم ينغتشو كبير في السن.
He already has one foot in the grave.
لقد وضع بالفعل قدماً في القبر.
I won't marry him.
لن اتزوجه
His age is indeed advanced,
عمره متقدم بالفعل
but the Governor of Yingzhou
لكن حاكم ينغتشو
has considerable influence at court.
لديه نفوذ كبير في المحكمة.
Xi,
شي،
you're about to become the principal daughter of the Zhou family.
أنت على وشك أن تصبح الابنة الرئيسية لعائلة تشو.
It's time for you
لقد حان الوقت لك
to contribute to our family.
للمساهمة في عائلتنا.
So you made me the Zhou family's principal daughter
لقد جعلتني الابنة الرئيسية لعائلة تشو
just to make my sacrifice more meaningful.
فقط لكي أجعل تضحياتي أكثر معنى.
How dare you speak like that!
كيف تجرؤ على التكلم بهذه الطريقة!
This marriage
هذا الزواج
is not yours to refuse!
ليس من حقك أن ترفض!
If you're unwilling,
إذا كنت غير راغب،
I'll have to go to the palace
سأضطر للذهاب إلى القصر
and request an imperial decree from His Majesty.
وطلب مرسومًا إمبراطوريًا من جلالته.
No need for that, Lord Zhou.
لا داعي لذلك، يا سيد تشو.
I've already
لقد فعلت ذلك بالفعل
obtained the decree for you.
حصلت على المرسوم لك.
[Deep Roots; Lush Branches]
[جذور عميقة؛ فروع خصبة]
Lord Zhou,
اللورد تشو،
I have requested permission from Father
لقد طلبت الإذن من الأب
to marry Miss Zhou Ruoxi.
للزواج من الآنسة Zhou Ruoxi.
I hope you will grant your approval.
أتمنى أن تمنح موافقتك.